{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I went to the same high school as Madonna.",
            "answer": "Ryan"
        },
        {
            "question": "I got my butt kicked by Jean Claude Van Damme.",
            "answer": "Ruta"
        },
        {
            "question": "I once danced for 30 hours straight without caffeine (or drugs).",
            "answer": "Anastasia"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have a fish named Bully, and he follows & swims alongside my finger.",
            "answer": "Amber"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was on the show Blue's Clues as a little kid.",
            "answer": "Elisabeth"
        },
        {
            "question": "My ancestors are from five continents.",
            "answer": "Elisabeth"
        },
        {
            "question": "I play the banjo.",
            "answer": "Elisabeth"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can make my tongue look like it's split down the middle.",
            "answer": "Elisabeth"
        },
        {
            "question": "I used to snore so loud that I had to get surgery to fix it",
            "answer": "Robi"
        },
        {
            "question": "On my 18th birthday I was arrested for vandalizing a police car.",
            "answer": "Annika"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have haunting dreams about penguins sometimes.",
            "answer": "Pim"
        },
        {
            "question": "I nearly slept on the hotel floor of a now 3x Grammy winning artist back when I was a teen..",
            "answer": "Pim"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was in a horse stampede and barely survived. ",
            "answer": "Caity"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have Synaesthesia, Hypergraphia, etc. ",
            "answer": "Caity"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know how to ride a bicycle.",
            "answer": "Mishka"
        },
        {
            "question": "I auditioned for X-Factor USA and they told me I sing too quietly.",
            "answer": "Maryse"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like to find stray kittens that have been abandoned by the cat mom, and raise it until I find them a new adoption family.",
            "answer": "Liyanbing"
        },
        {
            "question": "I make my own ice cream.",
            "answer": "Ian"
        },
        {
            "question": "I once went through airport security with a bullet case in my boots.",
            "answer": "Maram"
        },
        {
            "question": "My undergraduate major at university was Human Biology.",
            "answer": "Craig"
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked as a movie trailer editor for several years at motion picture advertising studio.",
            "answer": "Craig"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was part of a military style drill team for 8 years.",
            "answer": "Kami"
        },
        {
            "question": "I peed the bed until I was 12.",
            "answer": "Kami"
        },
        {
            "question": "I used to have a band named Sabbatical in college.",
            "answer": "Jonny"
        },
        {
            "question": "I won a blind chess tournament by only moving one piece.",
            "answer": "Eric"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wanted to become a professional figure ice skater when i was a kid.",
            "answer": "Jaiden"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was part of a sorority in undergrad.",
            "answer": "Jaiden"        },
        {
            "question": "I went to three different colleges in my undergrad.",
            "answer": "Jaiden"        },
        {
            "question": "I've written several different screenplays including two episodic ones and only three made it into production.",
            "answer": "Jaiden"        },
        {
            "question": "The last book I fully read was Mockingjay.",
            "answer": "Jaiden"        }	
    ]
}